Guide to the Carl Djerassi Papers SC0348
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Mass Spectra Notebooks, Series 6 (Box 28-41)
  - Eadon (2) (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Failli (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Fajkos (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Faul (1) (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Faul (2) (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Faul (3) (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Fenselan (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Ferreira (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Finch (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Fischer (1) (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Fischer (2) (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Flores (1) (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Flores (2) (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - George (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Goldsmith (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Gore (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Gray (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Green (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Gurst (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Gutzwiller (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Hammerum (1) (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Hammerum (2) (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Harris, R. (1) (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Harris, R. (2) (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Harrison (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Hart (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Isser (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Jones (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Joule (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Kaisin (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Kielcszewski (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Klein (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Knight (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Komitsky (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - La Londe (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Laur (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Le Clerq (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Lee (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Li (1) (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Li, X (2) (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Li, X (3) (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Liedtke (1) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Liedtke (2) (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Liedtke (3) (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Liedtke (4) (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Liedtke (5) (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Lightner (1) (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Lightner (2) (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Ling (1) (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Ling (2) (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Lund (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - MacLeod (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Manni (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Marx (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Mayer (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - McCrindle (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Midgley (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Milborrow (1) (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Milborrow (2) (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Monteiro (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Murray (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Nakagawa (1) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Nakagawa (1) (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Nakagawa (2) (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Nakagawa (3) (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Nakagawa (4) (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Nakano (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Ohashi (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Osiecki (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Owellen (1) (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Owellen (2) (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Pak (1) (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Pak (2) (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Partridge (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Patterson (1) (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Patterson (2) (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Patterson (3) (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Pelah (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Popov (1) (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Popov (2) (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Popov (3) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Popov (4) (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Powell (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Powers (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Reusch (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Robertson (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Roller (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Rothberg (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Sample (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Schneider (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Shapiro (1) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Shapiro (2) (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Shapiro (3) (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Spangler (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Staunton (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Steiner (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Strong (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Sundaraman (1) (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Sundaraman (2) (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Suyat (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Suzuki/Seidel/Westley/Mayer (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Swanholm (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Taylor (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Theobald (1) (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Theobald (2) (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Thomson (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Tokes (1) (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Tokes (2) (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Tokes (2) (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Tolela (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Tomer (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Trudell (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Tursch (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Undheim (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Vanderah (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Vanderwale (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Van Horne (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Voelter (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Von Mutzenbecher (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Vor Brueggen (1) (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Vor Brueggen (2) (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Walser (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Warawa (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Weidler (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Weinberg (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Wilkinson (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Williams (1) (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Williams (2) (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Wolf (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Woodgate (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Wyllie (1) (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Wyllie (2) (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Zielinske (1) (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Zielinske (2) (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Zielinske (3) (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Unknown (CD Spectra), 1980 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Research Files, Series 7
  - Subject Files
    - Aspidosperma: Refractive (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
    - Aspidosperma: B. Gilbert (Box 1, Folder 4-8)
    - Butea Superba (Box 1, Folder 9-10)
    - Cafestol (Box 1, Folder 11-13)
    - Cafestol: Sengupta (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Aspidofiline (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Aspidosperma: Misc. (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
    - Aspidosperma: Cylindrocarpine (Box 2, Folder 5-6)
    - Compactinerrin (Box 2, Folder 7-8)
    - Erythromycin (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Iresin (Box 2, Folder 10-13)
    - Peniocereus (Box 3, Folder 1-5)
    - Petasin (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Plant Collections (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Refractidine (Box 3, Folder 8-9)
    - Skytanthine (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Jegosapogenol (Box 3, Folder 11-12)
    - Spegazzinine (Diabolin) (Box 3, Folder 13-14)
    - Stemmadenine (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Vallesia Dichotoma (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Tlatlancuayin (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Vindolinine (Box 4, Folder 4-5)
  - Files Arranged by Researcher
    - Adelstein, Dr. Gilbert W. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Anderson, Gary (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Antonaccio, Libero D. (Box 5, Folder 3-4)
    - Arndt, Reinhard R. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Bachman, Paul L. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Bannick, Mark (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Barnes, Charles (Box 5, Folder 8-9)
    - Beard, Colin (Box 5, Folder 10-11)
    - Beechan, Curtis Michael (Box 5, Folder 12-13)
    - Bengelmans, Rene (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Bianchi, Ennio (Box 5, Folder 15-16)
    - Blossey, Erich C. (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Brandt, Rogert D. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Briat, Bernard (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Briggs, Scott (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Brockman, Hans H., Jr. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Brown, Charles A. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Brown, Frederick (Box 6, Folder 6-8)
    - Brown, Keith S., Jr. (Box 6, Folder 9-10)
    - Brown, Peter (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Brown, Stuart (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Bruckmann, Edith (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Buchs, Armand (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Bunnenberg, E. (Box 6, Folder 15-16)
    - Burke, Basil (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Bendas (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Burrows, Brian (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Cable, John (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Carlson, Robert M. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Chamberlain, J. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Carpenter, Wayne (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Cheer, Clair (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Cook, Michael M. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Daloze, D. (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Dawson, John (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - De Amicis, Carl (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Delseth, Claude (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - De Martino, G. (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Demirev, Plamen (Box 7, Folder 13)
    - Dias, Jerry Ray (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Diekman, John D. (Box 7, Folder 15)
    - Dillon, Diane (Box 7, Folder 16)
    - Dixon, Scott (Box 7, Folder 17)
    - Dolinger, Peter (Box 7, Folder 18)
    - Duffield, Alan (Box 7, Folder 19)
    - Eadon, George (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Eckstein, Heiner (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Edgar, Mark (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - Elder, Danny Lee (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - Failli, Dr. Amadeo A. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Fajkos, J. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Fenselau, Catherine (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Ferreira, Joaquim M. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - Fischer, Martin (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Fisher, Larry (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Fitch, William L. (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Fritz, Helmut (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Photos and negatives – temporary home ["peniocereus," "wilcoxia viperina" and "cafestol"] (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - Gaete-Holmes, Richard (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Gebreyesus, Tarekegu (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Gerrard, Allan F. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Gore, Jacques (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Gorthey, LeeAnn (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Grant, Barbara Dianne (Box 9, Folder 6-7)
    - Green, Mark M. (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Glaar, Fazil (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Gutzwiller, Jurg (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Haley, Michael (Box 9, Folder 11-12)
    - Hamlet, Zacharias (Box 9, Folder 13)
    - Hammerum, Steen (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - Harel, Zvi (Box 9, Folder 15)
    - Harris, Ralph N., III (Box 9, Folder 16)
    - Harris, Roger L. N. (Box 9, Folder 17)
    - Harrison, I. (Box 9, Folder 18-19)
    - Herbst, David (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Ikeda, Dr. Masazumi (Box 10, Folder 2-3)
    - Isser, Stephen J. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Jaeger, David (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Joseph, Jack (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Jones, Geraint (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Joule, John A. (Box 10, Folder 8-9)
    - Kasin, Michel (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - Kan, Peter (Tai-Yuen) (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - Katoh, Masanobu (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - Keegan, Joseph (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - Kempf, Karl (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - Klein, Harald (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - Kielczewski, Michal (Box 10, Folder 16-17)
    - Kielczewski, Michal (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - Knierzinger, Andreas (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - Koch, Patrick (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Komitsky, Frank (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Konopelski, Joe (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Kossanni, Jean (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Kramar, Jaraslov (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - LaLonde, Robert T. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Lankelma, Jan (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Laur, Peter H. A. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Lee, Shy-Fuh (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Liedtke, Raymond (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Lightner, David (Box 11, Folder 13-14)
    - Lindley, Matthew (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - Ling, Nicholas Chi-Kwan (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Lu, Yu-Cheng (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
    - MacLeod, John K. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Manni, Peter E. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Marx, Dr. Michael (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Marshall, Dennis (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Massey, Ian (Box 12, Folder 9-10)
    - Mayer, Klaus K. (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - McCrindle, Robert (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Midgley, Ian (Box 12, Folder 13)
    - Millborrow, Dr. Barry V. (Box 12, Folder 14)
    - Mo, Yoke (Box 12, Folder 15)
    - Moldowan, J. Michael (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Monteiro, Hugo Jorge (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Morizur, J. P. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Morrill, Kent (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Muccino, Richard (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Nakano, Tatsuihiko (Box 13, Folder 6-8)
    - Nakano, Tatsuihiko (Steroids) (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Nordstrom, Carla (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Ohashi, Mamoru (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Osiecki, Jeanne (Box 13, Folder 12-16)
    - Partridge, Les (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Patterson, Donald (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Pelah, Dr. Zvi (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
    - Powell, Harold (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Powers, Thomas W. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Rudler, Michele C. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Sanchez, Wolfgang (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Schroll, Gustav (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Shapiro, R. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Sheehan, Michael M. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Simek, Jan (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Sing, Yuen-Lung Lawrence (Box 14, Folder 13-14)
    - Singy, Gerard (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Sjoberg, Berndt (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
    - Smith, Grant G. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Spangler, Dr. Richard J. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Spiteller, Gerhard (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Staunton, James (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Stenhagen, Einar (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Strong, M. Karen (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Suchy, Milos (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Sundararamen, P. (Box 15, Folder 10-11)
    - Suyat, Reginald (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Taylor, Evelyn (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Tater, Christopher B. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Thieberg, K. (Paciorek) (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - Thomas, G. H. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Thomson, James B. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Tokes, Lazlo (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Tolela, Marcus Luhata (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Tomer, Kenneth (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Trudell, James R. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Tursch, Bernard M. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Undheim, Kjell (Box 16, Folder 10-11)
    - Vairamani, Mariappandar (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Van Antwerp, Craig (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Vanderah, David (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Vandewalle, M. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Van Horn, Albert (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Vietmeyer, Noel D. (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Voelter, Dr. Wolfgang (Box 17, Folder 3-5)
    - Von Mutzenbecher, Gerhard (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Vorgrueggen, Helmut (Box 17, Folder 7-9)
    - Waespe-Sarcevic, Nada (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Wee, Andrew (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Weidler, Anne-Marie (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Weinberg, David S. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Weinheimer, Alfred J. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Wiersig, James (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Wellman, Keith (Box 18, Folder 7-8)
    - Woodgate, Paul D. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Williams, Dudley H. (Box 18, Folder 10-11)
    - Wolff, Robert (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Wyllie, S. Grant (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Wunderlich, Edgar (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Yang, Shi-Ying (Box 19, Folder 40911)
    - Yaeger, Ernest (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Yeo, Adrian (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Zeeh, Dr. Bernd (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Rotary Dispersion Correspondence, Series 8
  - A (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Briggs, Prof. L. H. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Buchi, George (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - B (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Collins, C. J. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Cram, Dr. D. J. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - C (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Dauben, W. G. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - D (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ehrenstein, Maximilian (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Engel, Prof. Charles R. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - E (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Fajkos, Dr. J. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Fieser, L. F. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Fishman, Dr. Jack (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Foss, Dr. John G. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Freudenberg, K. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - F (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - G (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - H (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Halsall, T. G. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Henbest, H. B. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Heront, Dr. V. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Herz, Werner (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Hodges, Dr. Richard (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Holker, J. S. E. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Inhoffen, Prof. H. H. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - I (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Jones, E. R. H. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Jacques, Jean (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Jefferies, P. R. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Jeger, O. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - J (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Kjaer, Anders (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Kupchan, Morris (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - K (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Lahey, F. N. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Lamberton, J. A. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Lederer, Prof. E. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Levi, Dr. Leo (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Levin, R. H. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Luttringhaus, Dr. A. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Lyle, Dr. Gloria G. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - L (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Marsh, Dr. Max (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Materials Research, Center For (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - McCasland, Dr. C. E. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Mislow, Kurt (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Mosettig, Erich (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Mukawa, Dr. Fumikazu (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - M (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - N (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Nickon, Dr. Alex (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Nussbaum, A. L. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - O (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Ohloff, Gunther (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Okuda, T. and Suzuki, M. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Ollis, W. D. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Owen, L. N. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - P (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Ponsold, Dr. K. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - R (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Reichstein, T. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Rudolph, Hellmuth (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Sarett, Dr. L. H. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Sengupta, Pasupati and Khastgir, H. N. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Sheppard, R. C. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Smissman, Edward E. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Spring, F. S. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Stephens, Dr. Philip J. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Summers, Dr. G. H. R. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - S (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - T (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Takeda, K. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Tamm, Dr. C. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Tanabe (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Tao, Dr. Rosaline C. C. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Tsuda, K. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - U (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - V (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Varian Associates (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - W (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Walborsky, H. M. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Warnhoff, E. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Weiss, Dr. Ulrich (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Whalley, W. b. (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - White, D. E. (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Wiesner, Dr. K. (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Wolfrom, M. L. (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Y (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Z (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Curves and Data Sheets 3800-3849 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Curves and Data Sheets 3850-3899 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Curves and Data Sheets 3900-3907 (Box 6)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1992-102
  - Lab Notebooks
    - Diek; JP-Morizur (189), 1967-1969 (Box 1, Volume 146)
    - Tarekegn Gebreyesus p. 100f; Stuart H. Brown; Prof. Carl Djerassi; Notebook D-II, 1967 Aug 2-1968 Apr 19 (Box 1, Volume 147)
    - No. 148 (Box 1, Volume 148)
    - David Schooley; A. [Gewert], 1965 Mar 2-1969 Aug 21 (Box 1, Volume 149)
    - [Spangler]; Weinheimer; [Sheehan]; [Dias], 1968 Jun 12-1972 Aug 25 (Box 1, Volume 150)
    - J. Trudell; M. Younus Sheikh, 1968 Jun 24-1970 Apr 12 (Box 1, Volume 151)
    - Brandt Rojer; John H. Block p. 247-270; Evelyn (Lyn) Taylor p. 273- (Box 1, Volume 152)
    - Masazumi Ikeda (page 1-205); Robin T. Gray (207-end); Index page 207, 1966 Sept 23-1968 Jan 9 (Box 1, Volume 153)
    - Robin T. Gray (continued from Book #153) February 1969-September 1969 (to page 61); Paul D. Woodgate ( Oct. 1969 pages 62-211); Carla Rae Nordstrom (January 1975), 1969 Feb 14-1977 Jan 10 (Box 1, Volume 154)
    - Book III; Book I is 122 (with A. Failli); Book II is 142; William H. Faul; Index p.p. 1-5; Research starts p. 6; Book I James L. Bowen; II J. Englebrecht p. 183, 1969 Apr 29-1972 (Box 1, Volume 155)
    - Michele Rudler (-pg. 19); Giovanni De Martino (from page 21); Beechan, Curt (from page 77, page 77 = table of contents); Table of Contents for Curtis Beechan's work starts on page 77, 1969-1973 (Box 1, Volume 156)
    - Notebook 156A (continuation of notebook 156); Curtis M. Beechan; Djerassi lab - Stanford University, 1972 Sept 11-1974 Nov 24 (Box 1, Volume 156A)
    - Curtis M. Beechan; This is notebook 156B which is a continuation of notebook 156A, 1974 Dec 5-1976 Apr 30 (Box 2, Volume 156B)
    - Notebook 156C (continuation of notebook 156B); Curtis M. Beechan; Djerassi Lab Group, 1976 May 4-1978 Feb (Box 2, Volume 156C)
    - Sample Box No. 65; S. Brown Chamberlain; Tarekegu Gebreyesus (1967-1971); Z. Hamlet (pp 153-), 1969 Nov 5-1973 Jul 11 (Box 2, Volume 157)
    - Roller; Dias, 1969 Mar 5-1971 May 7 (Box 2, Volume 158)
    - M. Younus Sheikh, 1970 Apr 24-1972 Mar 9 (Box 2, Volume 159)
    - Younus Sheikh; Aug 9 1973, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Volume 159A)
    - Muhammad Younus Sheikh, 1972 Mar 12-1973 (Box 2, Volume 159B)
    - Klaus Mayer 1970; Barbara Grant 1971; Nada Waespe-Sarcevic, 1970 Jun 9-1976 (Box 2, Volume 160)
    - C. Djerassi; research of Thomas W. Powers; Scott Dixon (Box 2, Volume 161)
    - David A. Jaeger; Stauffer I - 1st Floor; J. M. Moldowan 10/72; Stauffer I - 1st Floor, 1970 Sept 10-1973 Apr 10 (Box 2, Volume 162)
    - Noel Vietmeyer (1-179); Ian Midgley (180-), 1968-1972 (Box 2, Volume 163)
    - A. Yeo; Robert Ghirardelli p. 13-137; John H. Block pp. 139-, 1971-1973 (Box 3, Volume 164)
    - Wai Lee Jan, 1971 Feb 2-1975 Mar 24 (Box 3, Volume 165)
    - Dr. C. Djerassi; I. Rothberg; Chem Department; Stanford University; Taylor, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Volume 167)
    - S. Eadon; Richard R. Muccino, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Volume 166)
    - Craig L. Van Antwerp, 1973 Mar 26-1977 Aug 17 (Box 3, Volume 168)
    - K. Tomer (1-174); G. Singy (175- ), 1972 (Box 3, Volume 169)
    - Research Jan. 71- Jan. 1974; William Fitch, 1971-1974 (Box 3, Volume 170)
    - W. Fitch 1974; J. W. Simek 1974-1975; Mattern 1975 (Box 3, Volume 171)
    - Robert D. Walkup, 1975 Jul 31-1978 Feb 14 (Box 3, Volume 173)
    - Box I; John H. Dawson; Stauffer I Building - 107c; March 3 1974 to July 13 1975, 1974 Mar 3-1975 Jul 13 (Box 3, Volume 174)
    - Simeon Popov; Ian J. Massey; Prof. C. Djerassi (Box 3, Volume 176)
    - Book II; John H Dawson; Stauffer I Building - 107c; July 14 1975 to, 1975 Jul 14-1976 Jul 27 (Box 3, Volume 175)
    - Prof. Carl Djerassi; Department of Chemistry; Stanford University; Stanford, Calif. 94305; Edith M. Bruckmann pages 1-185; [P. Julaeon] pages 185- (Box 4, Volume 177)
    - Kent Morrill; Chem. Dept. Stanford Univ.; Stanford Ca 94305; S. Lee, 1972-1975 (Box 4, Volume 178)
    - Sample Box #160 and 162; Delseth Claude; Chem. Dept.; Stanford Univ., Ca 94305; 1019 Laurel St. Menlo Park, Ca 94205 (Box 4, Volume 180)
    - Donald G. Patterson Jr. pg. 1-109; Mark A. Bannick pg. 110-, 1977-1978 (Box 4, Volume 181)
    - Joseph P. Konopelski; See index at end of this notebook, 1977 (Box 4, Volume 183)
    - Robert Douglas Walkup, 1978 Feb 13-1979 Aug 5 (Box 4, Volume 184)
    - Tarekegn Gebreyesus; Sample boxes 65 & 142; Claudio Tarchini S. Box 137 (pages 68- ), 1977 Aug 29-1979 Mar 19 (Box 4, Volume 185)
    - J. S. McCallum (Djerassi lab); Robert D. Walkup (pp. 117-297); Dept. of Chemistry; Stanford University; Stanford, CA 94305 (415) 497-2858, 1980-1981 (Box 4, Volume 186)
    - Jill Moormeier; October 1977-, 1977 Oct 11-1979 Feb 11 (Box 4, Volume 187)
    - Karl Djerassi; and M. Wahid Khalil Book 2; Book III; 1978-1979; Stanford University; Dept. of Chemistry (Box 4, Volume 188)
    - Mark Edgar 10-19-78; 189; [O. Vilet], 1978-1982 (Box 4, Volume 189)
    - Yuen-Lung Lawrence Sing; Mathew Lindley; Ralph Harris, 1978 Nov 9-1981 Apr 1 (Box 5, Volume 190)
    - Zvi Harel; November 1979; J. Keegan; [O. Vilel], 1978 Nov 7-1983 Mar 2 (Box 5, Volume 191)
    - Martin Karpf; Continued book Nr. 92A, 1979 Oct 10-1981 Jan 26 (Box 5, Volume 192)
    - Richard Gaete-Holmes, 1979 (Box 5, Volume 193)
    - Frederick J. Brown; Notebook III; #194, 1981 (Box 5, Volume 194)
    - Ernest Kho-Wiseman; 8-79, 1979 Aug 6-1981 Mar 8 (Box 5, Volume 195)
    - Pierre-Alain Blanc; Number 196; Stanford University; Dept. of Chemistry; Sample box #171; [rows] D & E, 1979 Oct 9-1980 Oct 20 (Box 5, Volume 196)
    - Jaroslav Kramar; Robert W. Lang (? p. 100- ); Prof. Dr. C. Djerassi; Chemistry Dept.; Stanford University; Stanford Ca 94305; Anal. samples R. W. Lang Box 171 Nr. W-01 till W-20, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Volume 198)
    - Notebook [RDW-D] #199; Robert D. Walkup, 1979 Oct 10-1980 May 28 (Box 5, Volume 199)
    - Sundar p. 1-139; CB Cooper p. 139-; Stockroom Account Number: 517, 1981 (Box 5, Volume 200)
    - Ulf I. Sjostrand, 1979-1982 (Box 5, Volume 201)
    - Li Lian-Niang, 1979 Oct 3-1982 Aug 30 (Box 5, Volume 202)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1995-168
  - Applications and reports submitted to Biotechnology Resources Branch of the N. I. H., 1976-1978 (Box 1)
- Additional Material, Accession ARCH-1999-021
  - Lab Notebooks
    - Dai, Meilleko and Bich Huong. 6/89. CHICHE. (Box 1)
    - Eggersdoofe, Manfred and Ayanoghi, Eser. (Box 1, Folder 197)
    - Kehres, Lisa A. 1982 -1984. and Sohail Malik. 1986 -1988. (Box 1, Folder 225)
    - Ayanoghi, Eser. (Box 1, Folder 231)
    - Ayanoghi, Eser. (Box 1, Folder 247)
    - Rabirowitz, Michael. 6/86 -6/87. Computer Group. (Box 1, Folder 254)
    - Cordeiro, L. (Box 1, Folder 260)
    - Cordeiro, Lucinda. 1982. (Box 1, Folder 265)
    - Rabirowitz, Michael. 6/87 -7/88. (Box 1, Folder 273)
    - Malik, Sohail. 1986 -1988. (Box 1, Folder 279)
    - Rabirowitz, Michael. 5/89 -1/90. (Box 1, Folder 282)
    - Rabirowitz, M. 1/29/90 -9/19/90. (Box 1, Folder 284)
    - Rabirowitz, M. 9/20/90 -5/7/91. (Box 1, Folder 285)
    - Michele, Rizzolio. (Box 2)
    - Malik, Sohail. 1986 -1988. (Box 2, Folder 277)
    - Rabirowitz, Michael. 7/88 -5/89. (Box 2, Folder 278)